Guide to the Virginia Nelson playbills collection, 1939-2007
George Mason University Libraries
  - Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts - "The King and I,", July 20, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Accent Dinner Theatre - "Born Yesterday,", August 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Shady Grove Music Fair - "The Peggy Fleming Show - A Concert on Ice", 1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - John F. Kennedy (JFK) Center for the Performing Arts - "A Moon for the Misbegotten,", 1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Hayloft Dinner Theatre - "Play It Again Sam,", January 4, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Emperor Henry IV," Featuring Rex Harrison, March 1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Sammy Davis Jr. Show, June 4, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Olney Theatre - "Da,", August 7, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Shady Grove Music Fair - "No No Nanette," Featuring Ruby Keeler and Cyril Ritchard, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - National Theatre - "Godspell,", 1974 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - National Theatre - "Noel Coward - In Two Keys," Featuring Anne Baxter, Hume Cronyn, and Jessica Tandy, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Shady Grove Music Theatre - Bette Midler in Concert, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Seesaw,", July 1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Eisenhower Theatre - "Summer,", August 1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - City Center Joffrey Ballet, November 1974 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "In Praise of Love," Featuring Rex Harrison and Julie Harris, November 1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Shady Grove Music Theatre - Rich Little and Patti Page, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Shady Grove Music Theatre - Paul Lynde, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ford's Theatre - "Gabrielle,", January 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Misanthrope,", February 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "An Evening with Margot Fonteyn, Rudolf Nureyev, Paolo Borotluzzi,", July 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Theatre - "Bubbling Brown Sugar,", August 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Treemonisha,", September 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Royal Family," Featuring Rosemary Harris, Sam Levene, November 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Pacific Overtures, December 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - National Theatre - "Bubbling Brown Sugar,", February 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - New York City Ballet, February 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Royal Danish Ballet, May 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Shirley MacLaine, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Shady Grove Music Theatre - "Me and Bessie,", 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Shady Grove Music Theatre - "A Little Night Music," featuring Jean Simmons and Hermione Gingold, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Annie,", March 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - New York City Ballet - George Balanchine and Jerome Robbins, Ballet Masters - Featuring Jacques d'Amboise, March 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Metropolitan Opera - "Il Trovatore,", June 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Porgy and Bess,", July 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Pippin,", August 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - National Theatre - "Appearing Nitely," Featuring Lily Tomlin, August 1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "A Chorus Line,", September 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Soviet Georgian Dancers with Tbilisi Polyphonic Choir, November 22, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Comedy with Music," Featuring Victor Borge, November 28, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Semmelweiss," Featuring Colin Blakely and Patricia Routledge, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Timbuktu," Featuring Eartha Kitt, January 1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "First Monday in October," Featuring Henry Fonda and Jane Alexander, February 1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Dracula," Featuring Raul Julia, Designed by Edward Gorey, June 1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Oh, Kay!,", August 1978 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Last of Mrs. Cheyney," Featuring Deborah Kerr, September 1978 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Platinum,", October 1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "On Golden Pond,", January 1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Gin Game," Featuring Jessica Tandy and Hume Cronyn, April 1979 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Feld Ballet, December 29, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Do You Turn Somersaults?" Featuring Mary Martin and Anthony Quayle, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Olney Theatre - "That Championship Season,", circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Royal Family,", circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Ford's Theatre - The American Dance Machine, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Evolution of the Blues,", May 1980 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Wolf Trap - Cleo Laine and John Dankworth, July 8, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - The Broadway Theatre - "Evita," Featuring Patti LuPone, Mandy Patinkin, Bob Gunton, September 1980 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - New York City Ballet - George Balanchine and Jerome Robbins, Ballet Masters - Featuring Jacques d'Amboise, October 1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Mixed Couples," Featuring Julie Harris, Geraldine Page, Rip Torn, November 1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Capital Center - World Professional Figure Skating Championship, December 15, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Dance Theatre of Harlem, February 1981 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Winslow Boy,", May 1981 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Barnum,", June 4, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The West Side Waltz," Featuring Katharine Hepburn and Dorothy Loudon, March 1982 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Medea,", April 1982 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - The Source Theatre - "Bent,", 1983 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - American Ballet Theatre - Featuring Mikhail Baryshnikov, January 1983 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "American Buffalo," Featuring Al Pacino, September 1983 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Agnes of God,", December 1983 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Ford's Theatre - "Mass Appeal," Featuring Milo O'Shea and Adam Redfield, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Woman of the Year," Featuring Lauren Bacall, January 1984 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Washington Opera, January 1984 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - New Playwrights Theatre - "Secret Honor - The Last Testament of Richard M. Nixon,", January 8, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Hexagon - "Capitol Follies,", March 8, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Apollo Victoria Theatre - "Starlight Express,", Mach 27, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - New Playwrights Theatre - "Spalding Gray,", April 16, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Thomas Jefferson Community Theatre - An Evening of Dance, May 26, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - National Theatre - "Cats," Featuring Charlotte d'Amboise, June 1984 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Warner Theatre - Lena Horne - The Lady and Her Music, June 12, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Master Class,", September 1984 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Warner Theatre - "Torch Song Trilogy," Featuring Estelle Getty, September 18, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Warner Theatre - "Sugar Babies," Featuring Mickey Rooney and Ann Miller, November 7, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Horizons - "Automatic Pilot,", 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Steve Silver - "Makin' Whoopee!,", 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Horizons - "Orgasmo Adulto Escapes from the Zoo,", February 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "My One and Only," Featuring Sandy Duncan and Tommy Tune, March 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger - "The Miser,", April 8, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The John Curry Skaters, August 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre - "La Cage Aux Folles,", September 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Liza in Concert - Featuring Liza Minnelli, September 14, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - American Ballroom Theatre, October 24, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Lillian," Featuring Zoe Caldwell, December 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Aren't We All?" Featuring Rex Harrison and Claudette Colbert, December 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Horizons - "Marathons '33,", 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Warner Theatre - "Tango Argentino,", 1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Acting Company,", May 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Ma Rainey's Black Bottom,", May 14, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Prince Edward Theatre - "Chess,", July 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - The Apollo - "I'm Not Rappaport,", July 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Mount Vernon Players - "Twelfth Night or What You Will,", August 8, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - National Theatre - "Broadway Bound," Featuring Jason Alexander, October 1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "A Raisin in the Sun,", November 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Perfect Party,", January 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Les Miserables," Featuring Colm Wilkinson and Terrence Mann, January 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New Playwrights Theatre - "Eleanora Duse,", January 10, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - National Theatre - "Ian McKellen - Acting Shakespeare,", March 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - National Theatre - "I'm Not Rappaport,", April 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Joffrey Ballet, April 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Festival On Ice, May 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "I Never Sang For My Father,", September 1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Breaking the Code," Derek Jacobi, Jenny Agutter, October 1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre - "The Night Hank Williams Died,", January 1988 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - London Palladium - "Ziegfeld,", April 1988 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Washington Ballet, May 1988 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Washington, Front and Center!, September 26, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Lisner Auditorium - The Washington Ballet, October 27, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Barbara Cook, December 1988 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Shear Madness,", December 1988 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Steel Magnolias,", March 1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Sophisticated Ladies,", April 1989 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Speed-the-Plow," Featuring Bob Balaban, Felicity Huffman, May 1989 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Washington Ballet, May 13, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Into The Woods,", June 1989 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Road to Mecca," Featuring Kathy Bates, August 1989 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Two for the Show," Featuring Donald O'Connor and Mickey Rooney, August 1989 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Gypsy,", September 1989 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Cocktail Hour,", September 1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - National Theatre - "Rumors,", November 1989 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Annie 2,", December 1989 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - What's Past is Prologue, circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ford's Theatre - "The Foreigner,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - American Playwrights Theatre - "Bricktop,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Ford's Theatre - "1000 Years of Jazz,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Duke of York's Theatre - "How The Other Half Lives,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Lazy Susan Dinner Theatre - "George M!,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Harlequin Dinner Theatre - "Do Black Patent Leather Shoes Really Reflect Up?,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pro Femina Theatre - "Marking Time,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre - Brendan Behan, circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ford's Theatre - "Elmer Gantry", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ford's Theatre - "Words and Music,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Warner Theatre - "The Tap Dance Kid,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Olney Theatre - "The Foreigner,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Church Street Theatre - "Fixin' to Die: A Visit to the Mind of Lee Atwater,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - National Theatre - "Bob Fosse's Dancin',", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Moiseyev Dance Company, circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Warner Theatre - "Ain't Misbehavin',", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ford's Theatre - Michael Feinstein in Concert, circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - American Playwrights Theatre - "The Golden Shadows - Old West Museum,", circa 1980s (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger - "The Merry Wives of Windsor,", 1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Ballet National de Marseille Roland Petit, January 1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "A Tuna Christmas,", January 1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Plymouth Theatre - "The Heidi Chronicles," Featuring Brooke Adams, Tony Shalhoub, David Hyde Pierce, January 1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Majestic Theatre - "The Phantom of the Opera,", January 1990 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Dance Theatre of Harlem, March 1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Broadhurst Theatre - "Aspects of Love,", June 1990 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Ethel Barrymore Theatre - "Lettice and Lovage," Featuring Maggie Smith, June 1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Shogun,", September 29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Abbey,", October 1990 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Morris A. Mechanic Theatre - "Tru," Featuring Robert Morse, October 1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Lend Me A Tenor,", November 1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Lisner Auditorium - Peter Allen, November 16, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Amahl and the Night Visitors,", December 1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Grand Hotel,", December 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Cirque du Soleil, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Round House Theatre - "Odd Jobs,", January 23, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - American Ballroom Theatre, February 5, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Lucifer's Child," Featuring Julie Harris, March 1991 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - The Broadway Theatre - "Miss Saigon," Featuring Lea Salonga and Jonathan Pryce, July 1991 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Palace Theatre - "The Will Rogers Follies - A Life in Revue,", July 1991 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Mandy Patinkin in Concert: Dress Casual, September 1991 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Studio Theatre - "When I Was A Girl I Used to Scream and Shout,", September 11, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - French Embassy Auditorium - American Chamber Orchestra, October 7, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - American Chamber Orchestra, December 1991 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - District Curators, Inc. - "Monster in a Box,", December 10, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - National Theatre - "Crazy For You,", January 1992 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Solitary Confinement," Featuring Stacy Keach, February 28, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Dawn Upshaw and Margo Garrett, March 1992 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Morris A. Mechanic Theatre - "Lost in Yonkers,", March 1992 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Neil Simon Theatre - "Jake's Women," Featuring Alan Alda, April 1992 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre - "Mother Courage and Her Children,", April 1992 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Royal Theatre - "Conversations With My Father," Featuring Judd Hirsch, Tony Shalhoub, David Margulies, Jason Biggs, April 1992 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Buddy,", May 1992 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - National Symphony Orchestra, November 1992 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Secret Garden,", December 1992 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - National Theatre - "A Tuna Christmas,", December 1992 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Virginia Theatre - "Jelly's Last Jam," Featuring Gregory Hines, December 1992 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre - "Romeo and Juliet,", 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - National Theatre - "Six Degrees of Separation," Featuring Marlo Thomas, April 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - The JFK Center for the Performing Arts - All Star Tap Revue, May 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Interact Theatre Co. - "Shirley Valentine,", May 14, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Marquis Theatre - "The Goodbye Girl," Featuring Bernadette Peters and Martin Short, June 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ethel Barrymore Theatre - "The Sisters Rosenweig," Featuring Jane Alexander, Madeline Kahn, June 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "The Twilight of the Golds," Featuring Jennifer Grey, July 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Morris A. Mechanic Theatre - "The Madness of George III" Featuring Nigel Hawthorne, October 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Radio City Music Hall - Christmas Spectacular, December 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - An Evening of Song with Barbara Cook, December 14, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre - "The Doctor's Dilemma,", 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Washington Opera, January 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Jackie Mason: Politically Incorrect, March 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Freedom Stage - "The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me,", July 28, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Some of My Best Friends Are the Blues,", October 1994 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Festival Australia, October 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Minskoff Theatre - "Sunset Blvd." Featuring Glenn Close, November 1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Gershwin Theatre - "Show Boat," Featuring Elaine Stritch, Lonette McKee, November 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - The London Palladium - "Oliver!,", December 8, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Performance Plus, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - The Washington Opera, February 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Rhinoceros,", March 8, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Angels in America,", May 1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Bessie's Blues,", May 3, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Angels in America,", June 1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Folger Elizabethan Theatre - "The Merchant of Venice,", June 3, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "Wanted,", June 12, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Master Class," Featuring Zoe Caldwell, September 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Metro Stage - "Me and Jezebel,", September 7, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Suzanne Farrell Stages Balanchine, October 17, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Smithsonian Institution - Omagari Taiko Dojo, November 1995 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "Rush Limbaugh in Night School,", November 6, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Three Sisters,", November 8, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Three Tall Women,", November 1995 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - Luisa Miller, November 1995 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Cort Theatre - "The Heiress," Featuring Cherry Jones, November 1995 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Oregon Shakespeare Festival - "Arcadia," "Moliere Plays Paris," "The Winter's Tale," "Awake and Sing!" "Strindberg in Hollywood," and "A Pair of Threes,", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Club Fugazi - "Beach Blanket Babylon,", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - The Shakespeare Theatre - "Volpone,", 1996 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "The Obituary Bowl,", January 29, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "My Heart Belongs to Tap,", February 1996 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "An Evening With Spalding Gray,", February 7, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Talking Heads,", March 6, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Curran Theatre - "The Phantom of the Opera," Featuring Franc D'Ambrosio, April 1996 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Warner Theatre - Forever Tango, April 16, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Signature Theatre - "Passion,", April 24, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - The Studio Theatre - "Suburbia,", May 1, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - The Smithsonian Associates - National Tap Dance Day, May 22, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Dupont Productions, LP - "Party,", May 31, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Woolly Mammorth Theatre Co. - "The Gigli Concert,", June 3, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Shear Madness,", July 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Signature Theatre - "The Rink,", August 21, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mount Vernon College - A Performance Cabaret, September 10, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Wyndham's Theatre - "ART,", October 4, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - JFK Center for the Performing Arts - "Mrs. Klen,", October 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Guise Theatre - "The Only Thing Worse You Could Have Told Me...,", November 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Woolly Mammoth Theatre Co. - "A Huey P. Newton Story,", November 8, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Richard Rodgers Theatre - "Chicago," Featuring Joel Grey, December 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - The Studio Theatre - "The Cryptogram,", December 11, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Nederlander Theatre - "Rent," Featuring Taye Diggs, Idina Menzel, Anthony Rapp, December 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Wolf Trap - Riverdance, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Statni Opera - "Eugene Onegin,", 1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Washington Stage Guild - "Murder in the Cathedral,", January 1, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Morris A. Mechanic Theatre - "Barrymore," Featuring Christopher Plummer, February 1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Warner Theatre - "Blood On the Fields,", February 5, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Palais Auersperg Konzerte (Concerts), March 3, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)